Guide to the Hudson River Day Line Records 1818-1949 MS 315
New-York Historical Society
- Series II. Bound Volumes, circa 1833-1948; 52 Linear feet (375 bound volumes)
  - SS Alida. Captain's returns, 1866 (Offsite-box HR-1, Volume SN-4)
  - SS Alida. Captain's returns, 1868 (Offsite-box HR-2, Volume SN-5)
  - SS Alida. Captain's returns, 1869 (Offsite-box HR-2, Volume SN-6)
  - SS Alida. Captain's returns, 1858 (Offsite-box HR-2, Volume SN-7)
  - SS Alida. Captain's returns, 1863 (Offsite-box HR-2, Volume SN-8)
  - SS Alida. Captain's returns, 1861 (Offsite-box HR-2, Volume SN-9)
  - SS Alida. Captain's returns, 1864 (Offsite-box HR-2, Volume SN-10)
  - SS Alida. Captain's returns, 1865? (Offsite-box HR-2, Volume SN-11)
  - SS Alida. Towing bills, 1857? (Offsite-box HR-3, Volume SN-12)
  - SS Anna. Unpaid bills, 1855-1868? (Offsite-box HR-3, Volume SN-13)
  - SS Anna. Record of collections, 1855-1856 (Offsite-box HR-3, Volume SN-14)
  - SS Anna. Record of collections?, 1857-1860? (Offsite-box HR-3, Volume SN-15)
  - SS Anna. Captain's returns, 1864 (Offsite-box HR-3, Volume SN-16)
  - SS Anna. Captain's returns, 1866 (Offsite-box HR-4, Volume SN-17)
  - SS Anna. Captain's returns, 1862 (Offsite-box HR-4, Volume SN-18)
  - SS Anna. Captain's returns, 1868 (Offsite-box HR-4, Volume SN-19)
  - SS Anna. Captain's returns, 1865? (Offsite-box HR-4, Volume SN-20)
  - SS Anna. Captain's returns, 1867 (Offsite-box HR-4, Volume SN-21)
  - SS Anna. Captain's returns, 1857 (Offsite-box HR-4, Volume SN-22)
  - SS Anna. Captain's returns, 1855 (Offsite-box HR-4, Volume SN-23)
  - SS Anna. Captain's returns, 1856 (Offsite-box HR-4, Volume SN-24)
  - SS Anna. Unidentified (Unpaid bills?), 1855-1868? (Offsite-box HR-5, Volume SN-25)
  - SS Anna. Captain's returns, 1858 (Offsite-box HR-5, Volume SN-26)
  - SS Anna. Captain's returns, 1861 (Offsite-box HR-5, Volume SN-27)
  - SS Anna. Captain's returns, 1860 (Offsite-box HR-5, Volume SN-28)
  - SS Anna. Captain's returns, 1859 (Offsite-box HR-5, Volume SN-29)
  - SS Anna. Captain's returns, 1863 (Offsite-box HR-6, Volume SN-30)
  - SS Austin. Miscellaneous accounts, 1853 (Offsite-box HR-6, Volume SN-31)
  - SS Austin. Captain's returns, 1855 (Offsite-box HR-6, Volume SN-32)
  - SS Austin. Captain's returns, 1856 (Offsite-box HR-6, Volume SN-33)
  - SS Cayuga. Captain's returns., 1863 (Offsite-box HR-7, Volume SN-34)
  - SS Cayuga. Captain's returns., 1858 (Offsite-box HR-7, Volume SN-35)
  - SS Cayuga. Captain's returns., 1861 (Offsite-box HR-7, Volume SN-36)
  - SS Cayuga. Captain's returns., 1866 (Offsite-box HR-7, Volume SN-37)
  - SS Cayuga. Captain's returns., 1856 (Offsite-box HR-7, Volume SN-38)
  - SS Cayuga. Captain's returns., 1857 (Offsite-box HR-7, Volume SN-39)
  - SS Cayuga. Check stubs, 1857-1858 (Offsite-box HR-8, Volume SN-40)
  - SS Cayuga. Captain's returns., 1867 (Offsite-box HR-7, Volume SN-41)
  - SS Cayuga. Captain's returns., 1855 (Offsite-box HR-7, Volume SN-42)
  - Various steamboats. Towing, 1859 (Offsite-box HR-8, Volume SN-43)
  - SS Cayuga. Record of collections?, 1850s-1860s? (Offsite-box HR-8, Volume SN-44)
  - SS Cayuga. Towing, 1851 (Offsite-box HR-8, Volume SN-45)
  - Various steamboats. Towing, 1859-1860 (Offsite-box HR-9, Volume SN-46)
  - SS Cayuga. Captain's returns., 1864 (Offsite-box HR-9, Volume SN-47)
  - SS Cayuga. Captain's returns., 1865 (Offsite-box HR-9, Volume SN-48)
  - SS Cayuga. Captain's returns., 1863? (Offsite-box HR-9, Volume SN-49)
  - SS Cayuga. Captain's returns., 1868 (Offsite-box HR-9, Volume SN-50)
  - SS Commerce. Miscellaneous accounts, 1853-1856 (Offsite-box HR-9, Volume SN-51)
  - SS Commerce. Captain's returns, 1855 (Offsite-box HR-9, Volume SN-52)
  - SS E. Corning Jr. Record of collections, 1856-1859 (Offsite-box HR-10, Volume SN-53)
  - SS E. Corning Jr. Captain's returns, 1856 (Offsite-box HR-10, Volume SN-54)
  - SS Mercury. Captain's returns, 1857 (Offsite-box HR-10, Volume SN-55)
  - SS Mercury. Record of collections, 1857 (Offsite-box HR-10, Volume SN-56)
  - SS Mercury. Captain's returns, 1858 (Offsite-box HR-10, Volume SN-57)
  - SS Mercury. Captain's returns, 1859 (Offsite-box HR-10, Volume SN-58)
  - SS Ontario. Captain's returns, 1867 (Offsite-box HR-10, Volume SN-59)
  - SS Ontario. Captain's returns, 1863 (Offsite-box HR-10, Volume SN-60)
  - SS Ontario. Captain's returns, 1858 (Offsite-box HR-11, Volume SN-61)
  - SS Ontario. Captain's returns, 1857 (Offsite-box HR-11, Volume SN-62)
  - SS Ontario. Captain's returns, 1856 (Offsite-box HR-11, Volume SN-63)
  - SS Ontario. Captain's returns, 1864 (Offsite-box HR-11, Volume SN-64)
  - SS Ontario. Captain's returns, 1868 (Offsite-box HR-11, Volume SN-65)
  - SS Ontario. Captain's returns, 1862 (Offsite-box HR-11, Volume SN-66)
  - SS Ontario. Record of collections, 1856-1859 (Offsite-box HR-11, Volume SN-67)
  - SS Ontario. Captain's returns, 1861 (Offsite-box HR-12, Volume SN-68)
  - SS Ontario. Captain's returns, 1869 (Offsite-box HR-12, Volume SN-69)
  - SS Ontario. Towing bills, 1858? (Offsite-box HR-12, Volume SN-70)
  - SS Ontario. Captain's returns, 1866 (Offsite-box HR-12, Volume SN-71)
  - SS Ontario. Captain's returns, 1865 (Offsite-box HR-12, Volume SN-72)
  - SS Oswego. Captain's returns, 1866 (Offsite-box HR-12, Volume SN-73)
  - SS Oswego. Towing, 1849 (Offsite-box HR-12, Volume SN-74)
  - SS Oswego. Ledger (expense/receipts), 1849 (Offsite-box HR-12, Volume SN-75)
  - SS Oswego. Record of collections?, 1853 (Offsite-box HR-13, Volume SN-76)
  - SS Oswego. Captain's returns, 1865 (Offsite-box HR-13, Volume SN-77)
  - SS Oswego. Unidentified, 1848-1849 (Offsite-box HR-13, Volume SN-78)
  - SS Oswego. Captain's returns, 1864 (Offsite-box HR-13, Volume SN-79)
  - SS Oswego. Captain's returns, 1858 (Offsite-box HR-14, Volume SN-80)
  - SS Oswego. Captain's returns, 1868 (Offsite-box HR-14, Volume SN-81)
  - SS Oswego. Captain's returns, 1867 (Offsite-box HR-14, Volume SN-82)
  - SS Oswego? Check stubs (Offsite-box HR-14, Volume SN-83)
  - SS Oswego. Captain's returns, 1861 (Offsite-box HR-14, Volume SN-84)
  - SS Oswego. Captain's returns, 1862 (Offsite-box HR-15, Volume SN-85)
  - SS Oswego. Captain's returns, 1857 (Offsite-box HR-15, Volume SN-86)
  - SS Oswego. Captain's returns, 1855 (Offsite-box HR-15, Volume SN-87)
  - SS Oswego. Captain's returns, 1856 (Offsite-box HR-15, Volume SN-88)
  - SS Schuyler. Captain's returns, 1866 (Offsite-box HR-15, Volume SN-89)
  - SS Schuyler. Captain's returns, 1865 (Offsite-box HR-15, Volume SN-90)
  - SS Schuyler and SS Seneca. Accounts, 1864 (Offsite-box HR-16, Volume SN-91)
  - SS Schuyler. Captain's returns, 1862 (Offsite-box HR-16, Volume SN-92)
  - SS Schuyler. Captain's returns, 1863 (Offsite-box HR-16, Volume SN-93)
  - SS Schuyler. Captain's returns, 1858 (Offsite-box HR-16, Volume SN-94)
  - SS Schuyler. Captain's returns, 1869 (Offsite-box HR-16, Volume SN-95)
  - SS Schuyler. Captain's returns, 1867 (Offsite-box HR-17, Volume SN-96)
  - SS Schuyler. Captain's returns, 1860 (Offsite-box HR-17, Volume SN-97)
  - SS Schuyler. Captain's returns, 1859 (Offsite-box HR-17, Volume SN-98)
  - SS Schuyler. Captain's returns, 1868 (Offsite-box HR-17, Volume SN-99)
  - SS Schuyler. Captain's returns, 1864 (Offsite-box HR-17, Volume SN-100)
  - SS Schuyler. Captain's returns, 1861 (Offsite-box HR-17, Volume SN-101)
  - SS Seneca. Captain's returns, 1866 (Offsite-box HR-17, Volume SN-102)
  - SS Seneca. Captain's returns, 1867 (Offsite-box HR-17, Volume SN-103)
  - SS Seneca. Captain's returns, 1868 (Offsite-box HR-17, Volume SN-104)
  - SS Seneca. Captain's returns, 1864 (Offsite-box HR-18, Volume SN-105)
  - SS Chauncey Vibbard? Passage book, 1867 (Offsite-box HR-18, Volume SN-106)
  - SS Mary Powell. Stock Book (Offsite-box HR-18, Volume SN-107)
  - SS Mary Powell. Passage reports, 1900-1901 (Offsite-box HR-18, Volume SN-108)
  - Letterpress copybook of Alfred White, 1864-1866 (Offsite-box HR-19, Volume SN-109)
  - Letters (Offsite-box HR-19, Volume SN-110)
  - Letterbook (Letters to Alfred Van Santvoord), 1862-1863 (Offsite-box HR-19, Volume SN-111)
  - Letterbook (Letters to Alfred Van Santvoord), 1863 (Offsite-box HR-19, Volume SN-112)
  - Letterbook (Letters to Alfred Van Santvoord), 1864 (Offsite-box HR-19, Volume SN-113)
  - Letterbook (Letters to Alfred Van Santvoord), 1865 (Offsite-box HR-19, Volume SN-114)
  - Letterbook (Letters to Alfred Van Santvoord), 1855 (Offsite-box HR-19, Volume SN-115)
  - Letterbook (Letters to Alfred Van Santvoord), 1855 (Offsite-box HR-19, Volume SN-116)
  - Letterbook (Letters to Alfred Van Santvoord), 1857-1859 (Offsite-box HR-20, Volume SN-117)
  - Letterbook (Letters to Alfred Van Santvoord) (Offsite-box HR-20, Volume SN-118)
  - Letterbook (Letters to Alfred Van Santvoord), 1857 (Offsite-box HR-20, Volume SN-119)
  - Letterbook (Letters to Alfred Van Santvoord), 1858 (Offsite-box HR-20, Volume SN-120)
  - Various steamboats. Miscellaneous accounts, 1850, 1860s (Offsite-box HR-20, Volume SN-121)
    Besides accounts, includes a transcript of a financial agreement between the Hudson River Towing Association and the owners of the Cayuga and Oswego, with meeting notes related to the agreement (1850).
  - Recapitulation of receipts and expenses for various steamboats, 1861-1868 (Offsite-box HR-20, Volume SN-122)
  - Letters, to September 1855 (Offsite-box HR-20, Volume SN-123)
  - Letterpress copybook of Alfred Van Santvoord, 1862-1864 (Offsite-box HR-20, Volume SN-124)
  - Letters, 1883-1895 (Offsite-box HR-21, Volume SN-125)
  - Letters, 1869-1870 (Offsite-box HR-21, Volume SN-126)
  - Letterpress copybook, Volume #2. August 1895-March 1896, 1895-1896 (Offsite-box HR-21, Volume SN-127)
    Sequence numbers 127-159 is a series of letterbooks numbered on the spine, with some gaps (#1, 11, 15, and 31 were not included in the original donation).
  - Letterpress copybook, Volume #3. March 1896-August 1896 (Offsite-box HR-21, Volume SN-128)
  - Letterpress copybook, Volume #4. August 1896-June 1897, 1896-1897 (Offsite-box HR-22, Volume SN-129)
  - Letterpress copybook, Volume #5. June 1897-May 1898, 1897-1898 (Offsite-box HR-22, Volume SN-130)
  - Letterpress copybook, Volume #6. May 1898-June 1899, 1898-1899 (Offsite-box HR-22, Volume SN-131)
  - Letterpress copybook, Volume #7. June 1899-May 1900, 1899-1900 (Offsite-box HR-22, Volume SN-132)
  - Letterpress copybook, Volume #8. May 1900-February 1901, 1900-1901 (Offsite-box HR-23, Volume SN-133)
  - Letterpress copybook, Volume #9. March 1901-September 1901 (Offsite-box HR-23, Volume SN-134)
  - Letterpress copybook, Volume #10. September 1901-1902? (Offsite-box HR-23, Volume SN-135)
  - Letterpress copybook, Volume #12. March 1903-September 1903 (Offsite-box HR-24, Volume SN-136)
  - Letterpress copybook, Volume #13. September 1903-June 1904, 1903-1904 (Offsite-box HR-24, Volume SN-137)
  - Letterpress copybook, Volume #14. June 1904-March 1905, 1904-1905 (Offsite-box HR-24, Volume SN-138)
  - Letterpress copybook, Volume #16., 1905-1906? (Offsite-box HR-25, Volume SN-139)
  - Letterpress copybook, Volume #17., 1906? (Offsite-box HR-25, Volume SN-140)
  - Letterpress copybook, Volume #18., 1906?-1907? (Offsite-box HR-25, Volume SN-141)
  - Letterpress copybook, Volume #19., 1907? (Offsite-box HR-26, Volume SN-142)
  - Letterpress copybook, Volume #20. September 1907-April 1908, 1907-1908 (Offsite-box HR-26, Volume SN-143)
  - Letterpress copybook, Volume #21. April 1908-August 1908 (Offsite-box HR-26, Volume SN-144)
  - Letterpress copybook, Volume #22. August 1908-January 1909, 1908-1909 (Offsite-box HR-27, Volume SN-145)
  - Letterpress copybook, Volume #23. January 1909-June 1909 (Offsite-box HR-27, Volume SN-146)
  - Letterpress copybook, Volume #24. June 1909-September 1909 (Offsite-box HR-27, Volume SN-147)
  - Letterpress copybook, Volume #25. September 1909-March 1910, 1909-1910 (Offsite-box HR-28, Volume SN-148)
  - Letterpress copybook, Volume #26. March 1910-August 1910 (Offsite-box HR-28, Volume SN-149)
  - Letterpress copybook, Volume #27. August 1910-January 1911, 1910-1911 (Offsite-box HR-28, Volume SN-150)
  - Letterpress copybook, Volume #28. January 1911-July 1911 (Offsite-box HR-29, Volume SN-151)
  - Letterpress copybook, Volume #29. July 1911-October 1911 (Offsite-box HR-29, Volume SN-152)
  - Letterpress copybook, Volume #30. October 1911-May 1912, 1911-1912 (Offsite-box HR-29, Volume SN-153)
  - Letterpress copybook, Volume #32. October 1912-March 1913, 1912-1913 (Offsite-box HR-30, Volume SN-154)
  - Letterpress copybook, Volume #33. March 1913-July 1913 (Offsite-box HR-30, Volume SN-155)
  - Letterpress copybook, Volume #34. July 1913-May 1914, 1913-1914 (Offsite-box HR-30, Volume SN-156)
  - Letterpress copybook, Volume #35. May 1914-November 1914 (Offsite-box HR-31, Volume SN-157)
  - Letterpress copybook, Volume #36. November 1914-September 1915, 1914-1915 (Offsite-box HR-31, Volume SN-158)
  - Letterpress copybook, Volume #37. September 1915-January 1922, 1915-1922 (Offsite-box HR-31, Volume SN-159)
  - Letterpress copybook of the Hudson River Day Line, Albany Office, General Agent W.B. Elmendorf. June 1906-September 1907, 1906-1907 (Offsite-box HR-32, Volume SN-160)
    Sequence numbers 160-170 and 172 comprise a set of letter books. There are gaps of missing dates that were not included in the original donation.
  - Letterpress copybook of the Hudson River Day Line, Albany Office, General Agent W.B. Elmendorf. June 1909-February 1910, 1909-1910 (Offsite-box HR-32, Volume SN-161)
  - Letterpress copybook of the Hudson River Day Line, Albany Office, General Agent W.B. Elmendorf. November 1905-November 1906, 1905-1906 (Offsite-box HR-32, Volume SN-162)
  - Letterpress copybook of the Hudson River Day Line, Albany Office, General Agent W.B. Elmendorf. November 1917-October 1918, 1917-1918 (Offsite-box HR-32, Volume SN-163)
  - Letterpress copybook of the Hudson River Day Line, Albany Office, General Agent W.B. Elmendorf. August 1913-May 1914, 1913-1914 (Offsite-box HR-32, Volume SN-164)
  - Letterpress copybook of the Hudson River Day Line, Albany Office, General Agent W.B. Elmendorf. September 1911-July 1912, 1911-1912 (Offsite-box HR-33, Volume SN-165)
  - Letterpress copybook of the Hudson River Day Line, Albany Office, General Agent W.B. Elmendorf. May 1914-September 1914 (Offsite-box HR-33, Volume SN-166)
  - Letterpress copybook of the Hudson River Day Line, Albany Office, General Agent W.B. Elmendorf. February 1910-August 1910 (Offsite-box HR-33, Volume SN-167)
  - Letterpress copybook of the Hudson River Day Line, Albany Office, General Agent W.B. Elmendorf. July 1912-April 1913, 1912-1913 (Offsite-box HR-33, Volume SN-168)
  - Letterpress copybook of the Hudson River Day Line, Albany Office, General Agent W.B. Elmendorf. April 1913-August 1913 (Offsite-box HR-33, Volume SN-169)
  - Letterpress copybook of the Hudson River Day Line, Albany Office, General Agent W.B. Elmendorf. July 1915?-November 1917, 1915?-1917 (Offsite-box HR-34, Volume SN-170)
  - Letter book of Hudson River Day Line Cashier., 1900?-1912 (Offsite-box HR-34, Volume SN-171)
  - Letterpress copybook of the Hudson River Day Line, Albany Office, General Agent W.B. Elmendorf. September 1914-May 1915, 1914-1915 (Offsite-box HR-34, Volume SN-172)
  - Landed and Received Reports, 1921 (Offsite-box HR-34, Volume SN-173)
  - Landed and Received Reports, 1922 (Offsite-box HR-35, Volume SN-174)
  - Landed and Received Reports, 1923 (Offsite-box HR-35, Volume SN-175)
  - Landed and Received Reports, 1924 (Offsite-box HR-35, Volume SN-176)
  - Landed and Received Reports, 1925 (Offsite-box HR-35, Volume SN-177)
  - Landed and Received Reports, 1926 (Offsite-box HR-36, Volume SN-178)
  - Landed and Received Reports, 1927 (Offsite-box HR-36, Volume SN-179)
  - Landed and Received Reports, 1928 (Offsite-box HR-37, Volume SN-180)
  - Landed and Received Reports, 1929 (Offsite-box HR-37, Volume SN-181)
  - Landed and Received Reports, 1930 (Offsite-box HR-38, Volume SN-182)
  - Landed and Received Reports, 1931 (Offsite-box HR-38, Volume SN-183)
  - Landed and Received Reports, 1932 (Offsite-box HR-39, Volume SN-184)
  - Landed and Received Reports, 1933 (Offsite-box HR-39, Volume SN-185)
  - Landed and Received Reports, 1934 (Offsite-box HR-40, Volume SN-186)
  - Landed and Received Reports, 1935 (Offsite-box HR-40, Volume SN-187)
  - Landed and Received Reports, 1936 (Offsite-box HR-41, Volume SN-188)
  - Landed and Received Reports, 1939 (Offsite-box HR-41, Volume SN-189)
  - Landed and Received Reports, 1940 (Offsite-box HR-42, Volume SN-190)
  - Landed and Received Reports, 1941 (Offsite-box HR-42, Volume SN-191)
  - Landed and Received Reports, 1942 (Offsite-box HR-43, Volume SN-192)
  - Landed and Received Reports, 1943 (Offsite-box HR-43, Volume SN-193)
  - Landed and Received Reports, 1944 (Offsite-box HR-44, Volume SN-194)
  - Landed and Received Reports, 1945 (Offsite-box HR-44, Volume SN-195)
  - Landed and Received Reports, 1937 (Offsite-box HR-45, Volume SN-196)
  - Landed and Received Reports, 1938 (Offsite-box HR-45, Volume SN-197)
  - Account book. Abram Van Santvoord re: Swiftsure Line, 1840-1844 (Offsite-box HR-46, Volume SN-198)
  - Ledger of Alfred Van Santvoord. April 1857-March 1861, 1857-1861 (Offsite-box HR-46, Volume SN-199)
  - Ledger, 1833-1845 (Offsite-box HR-47, Volume SN-200)
  - Ledger, 1833-1845 (Offsite-box HR-47, Volume SN-201)
  - Hudson River Steamboat Company. Journal, 1845-1869 (Offsite-box HR-48, Volume SN-202)
  - Cash book, 1882-1883 (Offsite-box HR-48, Volume SN-203)
  - Ledger of Alfred Van Santvoord. March 1861-March 1864, 1861-1864 (Offsite-box HR-49, Volume SN-204)
  - Ledger of Alfred Van Santvoord. March 1864-March 1866, 1864-1866 (Offsite-box HR-49, Volume SN-205)
  - Ledger of Alfred Van Santvoord. March 1866-March 1880, 1866-1880 (Offsite-box HR-50, Volume SN-206)
  - Unidentified (Ledger?) (Offsite-box HR-51, Volume SN-207)
  - Unidentified (Ledger?) (Offsite-box HR-52, Volume SN-208)
  - Ledger (Offsite-box HR-52, Volume SN-209)
  - Cash book of Alfred Van Santvoord, 1883-1901 (Offsite-box HR-53, Volume SN-210)
    Sequence numbers 210-212 are a set of three cash books spanning 1883-1901. Sequence number 203 may be part of these as well.
  - Cash book of Alfred Van Santvoord, 1883-1901 (Offsite-box HR-53, Volume SN-211)
  - Cash book of Alfred Van Santvoord, 1883-1901 (Offsite-box HR-53, Volume SN-212)
  - Unidentified (Ledger?) (Offsite-box HR-54, Volume SN-213)
  - Ledger. Day Line Steamers, 1865-? (Offsite-box HR-55, Volume SN-214)
  - Unidentified. (Ledger? Day Line Steamers?), 1860s-1870s? (Offsite-box HR-56, Volume SN-215)
  - Ledger. Day Line Steamers, 1870s (Offsite-box HR-57, Volume SN-216)
  - Ledger? Hudson River Day Line, 1879-1884? (Offsite-box HR-58, Volume SN-217)
    Sequence numbers 218-221 and 234-238, and possibly this number 217, are a set of 10 ledgers spanning 1879-1914.
  - General Ledger. Hudson River Day Line, 1885-1888 (Offsite-box HR-59, Volume SN-218)
  - General Ledger. Hudson River Day Line, 1889-1893 (Offsite-box HR-60, Volume SN-219)
  - General Ledger. Hudson River Day Line, 1894-1896 (Offsite-box HR-61, Volume SN-220)
  - General Ledger. Hudson River Day Line, 1897-1899? (Offsite-box HR-62, Volume SN-221)
  - Uptows, from September 1856 (Offsite-box HR-63, Volume SN-222)
  - Uptows, to September 1856 (Offsite-box HR-63, Volume SN-223)
  - Coal accounts, 1855-1858 (Offsite-box HR-63, Volume SN-224)
  - Bills of lading for coal, ?-1868 (Offsite-box HR-63, Volume SN-225)
  - Bills of lading for coal, 1863-1864 (Offsite-box HR-64, Volume SN-226)
  - Bills of lading for coal, 1861-1862 (Offsite-box HR-63, Volume SN-227)
  - Bills of lading for coal, 1857-1858 (Offsite-box HR-64, Volume SN-228)
  - Scrapbook, circa 1903-1905 (Offsite-box HR-64, Volume SN-229)
  - Scrapbook? (Offsite-box HR-65, Volume SN-230)
  - Uptows, 1855 (Offsite-box HR-65, Volume SN-231)
  - Uptows, 1857 (Offsite-box HR-65, Volume SN-232)
  - Record of coal contracts, 1855-1869 (Offsite-box HR-65, Volume SN-233)
  - Ledger. Hudson River Day Line, 1900-1902? (Offsite-box HR-66, Volume SN-234)
  - Ledger. Hudson River Day Line, 1903-1905? (Offsite-box HR-67, Volume SN-235)
  - Ledger. Hudson River Day Line, 1906-1908? (Offsite-box HR-68, Volume SN-236)
  - Ledger. Hudson River Day Line, 1909-1912? (Offsite-box HR-69, Volume SN-237)
  - Ledger. Hudson River Day Line, 1913-1914? (Offsite-box HR-70, Volume SN-238)
  - Cash book. Hudson River Day Line, 1890-1891? (Offsite-box HR-71, Volume SN-239)
    Sequence numbers 239-246 comprise a set of cash books. The donation included an additional cash book, which is likely one of the unidentified volumes in the container list. In total, the dates span 1882-83 and 1887-1909.
  - Cash book. Hudson River Day Line, 1892-1895? (Offsite-box HR-71, Volume SN-240)
  - Cash book. Hudson River Day Line, 1896-1897? (Offsite-box HR-72, Volume SN-241)
  - Cash book. Hudson River Day Line, 1898-1901? (Offsite-box HR-72, Volume SN-242)
  - Cash book. Hudson River Day Line, 1902-1904? (Offsite-box HR-73, Volume SN-243)
  - Cash book. Hudson River Day Line, 1905-1906? (Offsite-box HR-73, Volume SN-244)
  - Cash book. Hudson River Day Line, 1907-1909? (Offsite-box HR-74, Volume SN-245)
  - Cash book. Hudson River Day Line, 1887-1889? (Offsite-box HR-74, Volume SN-246)
  - Day book. Hudson River Day Line, 1894-1896 (Offsite-box HR-75, Volume SN-247)
  - Ledger balances and trial balances. Hudson River Day Line, circa 1883-1917 (Offsite-box HR-75, Volume SN-248)
    Sequence numbers 248, 250, and 251 comprise a set of three ledger/trial balances, spanning 1883-1917.
  - Alfred Van Santvoord account (payments on his personal account) with Hudson River Day Line, and Eben Olcott account, 1897-1900 (Offsite-box HR-75, Volume SN-249)
  - Ledger balances and trial balances. Hudson River Day Line, circa 1883-1917 (Offsite-box HR-75, Volume SN-250)
  - Ledger balances and trial balances. Hudson River Day Line, circa 1883-1917 (Offsite-box HR-76, Volume SN-251)
  - SS Austin. Collections & running expenses account book, 1853-1856 (Offsite-box HR-75, Volume SN-252)
  - Ledger. Mary Powell Steamship Company, 1910? (Offsite-box HR-75, Volume SN-253)
  - Account. Eben Olcott, Mary Powell Steamship Company, People's Line, 1910-1911 (Offsite-box HR-76, Volume SN-254)
  - Ledger. Mary Powell Steamship Company, 1911? (Offsite-box HR-78, Volume SN-255)
  - SS Chauncey Vibbard. Passage book., 1874-1876 (Offsite-box HR-76, Volume SN-256)
  - Estimates, 1856-1857 (Offsite-box HR-77, Volume SN-257)
  - SS Peter Stuyvesant. Bible (Offsite-box HR-77, Volume SN-258)
  - SS DeWitt Clinton. Bible (Offsite-box HR-77, Volume SN-259)
  - SS Chauncey M. Depew. Bible (Offsite-box HR-77, Volume SN-260)
  - Towing, 1858 (Offsite-box HR-78, Volume SN-261)
  - Downtows, 1861 (Offsite-box HR-78, Volume SN-262)
  - Downtows, 1865 (Offsite-box HR-78, Volume SN-263)
  - Downtows, 1863 (Offsite-box HR-79, Volume SN-264)
  - Downtows, 1864 (Offsite-box HR-79, Volume SN-265)
  - Downtows, 1858 (Offsite-box HR-79, Volume SN-266)
  - Checkbook, 1859-1861 (Offsite-box HR-79, Volume SN-267)
  - Checkbook, 1866-1867 (Offsite-box HR-79, Volume SN-268)
  - Checkbook, 1863-1865 (Offsite-box HR-79, Volume SN-269)
  - Checkbook (Offsite-box HR-79, Volume SN-270)
  - Checkbook (Offsite-box HR-79, Volume SN-271)
  - Checkbook, 1862-1866 (Offsite-box HR-79, Volume SN-272)
  - Checkbook, 1864-1866 (Offsite-box HR-79, Volume SN-273)
  - Checkbook (Offsite-box HR-79, Volume SN-274)
  - Downtows, 1856 (Offsite-box HR-80, Volume SN-275)
  - Unpaid bills, 1855 (Offsite-box HR-80, Volume SN-276)
  - Unpaid bills, 1858 (Offsite-box HR-80, Volume SN-277)
  - Unpaid bills, 1857 (Offsite-box HR-80, Volume SN-278)
  - Unpaid bills, 1855-1856 (Offsite-box HR-81, Volume SN-279)
  - SS E. Corning Jr. Unpaid bills (Offsite-box HR-81, Volume SN-280)